(Penny:)Really? For a wedding?
(Amy:)You're right.
My cheek bones and beckoning pelvis...
(Amy:)...already have a certain
"Hello, sailor" quality.
I'm ready.
(Leonard:)Aw.
(Penny:)So handsome.
(Penny:)Like James Bond.
(Sheldon:)Better than James Bond
because he's tinier.
(Amy:)I got you this to give to me.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, guests don't normally
wear corsages to a wedding.
(Penny:)That's more of a prom thing.
(Amy:)I never went to my prom.
(Amy:)My mom paid my cousin to take me
but he just used the money to buy drugs.
(Penny:)Put the corsage on her.
Amy, this is for you, heh.
(Amy:)When you're done copping a feel,
that goes on my wrist.
All aboard. Woo-woo!
(Sheldon:)It's official. I'm an HO trainiac.